It's cold...
寒いといったり...
If only I knew...
それは もう...知ってれば...
Please eat...
食べてください...
yes...
はい...
It's really cute...
やっぱり可愛いね...
So cute...
可愛いね...
めっちゃ可愛い...
I'll change it a bit.
ちょっと、改めます
Oh, I feel like... really, that...
え、なんか、その...本当に、その...
Like this.
こうやって
wait a minute.
ちょっと待って
Please call the research student yesterday.
昨日、研究生を呼んでください
postgraduate?
研究生?
I agree.
そうですね
So, first of all, on that day,
で、まずこうやって、その日の、に、
It's like it's my responsibility.
俺の責任みたいな
Ah, I'm following you.
あ、ついてきてる
Have you stopped doing this?
これやめちゃったの?
picture?
え?
Have you just quit?
やめたて?
Blurry?
ぼやぼや?
I agree.
そうですね
picture?
え?
why?
なんで?
Somehow,
なんか、
Wait a minute, ah, is that so?
ちょっと、 あ、そうなの?
And I felt like I couldn't continue.
で、続けられないなとか
So, well, I kind of quit yesterday.
で、まあ、ちょっと昨日をやめた
Ah, that's right.
あ、そうなんだ
No, but we can really meet each other.
いや、でも、本当に会えるんだね
No, like a real idol.
いや、本物のアイドルみたいな
This is how we can meet.
こうやって会えるんですね
But as a research student.
でも、研究生で
No, but I mean, I've been on TV.
いや、でも、だって、テレビとか出たことあるの
Right?
でしょ
Just a little bit, it's not like we're going to do it in Vienna or something like that.
ちょっとだけ、そんなに、 ウィーンとかでやるわけではなくて、
It seems like it's just me.
ちょっと、俺だけみたいな
No, but it's amazing.
いや、でも、すごいじゃん
Hey.
ね え
Didn't you tell me the name of the group?
グループ名を教えてくれなかった?
Ah, yes.
あ、そう
Group name.
グループ名
That's a little normal.
それは、ちょっと、普通に
Well, but, well, well.
まあ、でも、そこそこ、まあ
Oh, oh.
ああ、ああ
That's amazing.
すごいね
The group name is like that, isn't it?
グ ループ名って、そんな、ねえ
That's fine, but.
それ いいじゃん、でも
No, but please don't say that.
いや、でも、言わないでくださいよ、
absolute.
絶対
Don't say it.
言わないで
That's... Oh, seriously.
それは、 あ、まじで
Please come as soon as you can.
入れたら早く来てください
That's amazing.
すごいね
It must have been difficult to get in.
入るの難しかったでしょ
Audition or something.
オーディションとか
Did you audition yourself?
オーディションで自分で受けた?
Yes, I auditioned.
はい、オーディションで受けた
Wait a minute, let's talk about idols.
ちょっと、アイドルって言ったら
No, at first, I mean,
いや、なんか、最初、 というか、
I've always had good employees,
ずっと従業が良かったんですけど、
It wasn't going well at all anymore, so...
もう、全然うまくいかなくて、 で、
For various reasons, for some reason,
いろいろ、 で、なんか、 から、
I started thinking, ``Maybe I should try my best.''
ちょっと、頑張っていようかな、 って 感じで始まって
That's right.
そうなんだ
No, I just want to support you.
いや、ちょっと、応援したい
ah.
あー
picture?
え?
That's right, everyone, to the members.
そのさ、みんなさ、 メンバーの人にさ、
Are you doing it with your voice?
声でやってるの?
The members were talking about this, and...
メンバー同士でそういう話で、 ちょっと、
It would be bad if they found out.
バレたらまずいから
Ah, I see.
あ、そっかそっか
Me, I didn't say that.
私 ね、言ってないです
I didn't say that.
言ってないんだ
yes.
はい
Then, of course, tell that to someone like the producer.
じゃあ、もちろん、その、プロデューサーみたいな人にも言って
do not have?
ない?
That's right, the person behind you.
そうですね、 後ろの人
But, like this, we'll meet.
でもさ、こういうさ、会うじゃん
There are people who say things like this,
こういうの、 言っちゃったりする人もさ、
Don't you say that?
言うんじゃない?
Is that okay?
あれ、大丈夫?
Don't say it anymore.
もう、言わないで
That's right.
そりゃそうだよね
Until now, then, like this,
これまでの、じゃあ、 こうやって、
How many times have we had a successful relationship?
うまく二人したのは、何回ぐらいある?
But only one person.
でも、一人だけです
Why is there only one person?
一人だけなんで?
That person?
という人?
The president's
社長さんの、
Only one person.
一 人だけです
So, am I the second person?
じゃあ、俺二人目?
This is the second person.
二人目です
That's amazing.
すごいじゃん
It's quite expensive, I'm paying for it.
結構、高いさ、 お金払っているさ、
It seems that there is no information about membership challenges or anything like that.
会員チャレンジとか、そういう情報が来ないらしい
Everyone, come and meet me.
みんなに、出会いに来て
Just wear this.
これだけ着て
Pretty good price.
結構、いい値段
What did you do with the president?
それ、社長さんとはさ、 何した?
I told him that he would take me out to eat, so
ご飯を、 連れてってくれるって話をしたので、
In a private room at a luxury hotel,
高級ホテルの、 なんか、個室で、
Hotel restaurant.
ホテルの、レストラン
That's what it feels like.
そういう感じです
I'm crying a little, so please watch the meal.
ちょっと泣いてるし、 で、ご飯をご視聴してください
Yeah.
うん
It's kind of like that, kind of like that.
その、 なんか、そういうさ、 なんか、
It's physical, it's social,
ようは、 体のね、 付き合い的な、
There are words.
言葉、ある
Ah, yes.
あ、そう
Once you go to the hotel, it doesn't end there.
ホテルに行くと、 それじゃ終わんない
Hey, as expected, I'm an idol too.
ちょっと、さすがに、 私も、アイドル、
I was doing it.
してた
Ah, at that time, I was already active.
あ、その頃は、もう、 現役だからね
Now's the time, I quit yesterday.
今こそ、昨日やめたけど
As expected.
さすがに
real?
ほんと?
Even though I know a lot about this, I still don't understand it.
こういうのは、 俺もあんま知ってても分かんないよね
It's just food.
食事だけだ
Doesn't it depend on the person?
人によるんじゃない?
I guess it depends on the person.
人によるんだろう
Basically, I'm invited, I'm invited,
基本的にはでもさ、 誘われる、 誘われる、
That's what I think.
と思うんだよ
Ah, I was invited by the president.
あ、社長に誘われた
To the president.
社長に
Did you know?
知ったの?
I didn't know.
知らなかった
oh dear,
まあ、
But how was it?
でも、 どうだった?
Today too, that's right, our original relationship...
今日も、 それさ、 元の付き合いが、
It seems sneaky.
ずるいみたいな
As expected.
さすがに
sorry.
ごめんなさい
yes.
はい
Like that, like that,
そういうふうに、 そういうふうに、
I was able to pull it off.
引 っ張れた
Won't you say it?
言わない?
still?
まだ?
Madakari?
まだかり?
difficult.
難しい
No, that's it, for example, money.
いや、それはさ、 たとえば、 お金、
The amount, isn't it?
金額、 そうじゃない?
There's no way it's happening at this point.
この時点でも発生してるわけない
Ah, that's good.
あ、いいじゃん
Anyway, I'm paying the debate, but...
とりあえず、 ディベーションも払ってるけど、
I would like to try it as a plus.
プラスにして、 してみたい
We still haven't gotten along at all.
まだ、全然仲良くなっていない
Me too.
俺もだって
That's fine.
それさ、いいじゃん
Do you remember?
覚えてる?
Is that really the case?
そもそも、 そ んなんですか?
I think I'll start.
始めると思う
No, the people at Fuyuya, their daily lives, etc.
いや、 冬屋の人、 それで、 生活とか、
That's what makes it fun.
楽しくなって、 っていうのは、 そこにあります
Well, that's right.
まあ、そうだよね
Because I still don't have a job.
まだだって、 仕事のない 状態だからね
Idols are like that, research students are like that.
アイドルだって、そんな、 研究生って、
I can't get that money, so...
そのお金もらえないのか、 だから、
Just a little bit.
ちょっと だけ
Well then, this is it.
じゃあ、これじゃん
yes.
そう
Okay.
いいよー
What is your experience?
経験は?
Experience with men?
男性経験?
Men's experience is so
男性経験は、 そんなに、
How many people?
何 人くらい?
I think I'm alone.
一人と思います
Really?
本当に?
But what happened when you were a research student?
でも、その研究生時代は、 あった?
do not have?
ない?
More and more.
どんどん
I was about to say something,
ちょっと、 ちょっと、 言いそうになって、
Isn't love prohibited or something?
恋愛禁止とか、 違う?
No, I just need to hurry up and wait a while.
いや、 や っぱ、 早く、 ちょっと、
a little bit,
ちょっと、
But, for some reason, I just...
でも、 なんか、せっかく、 ちょっと、
Still, please help me.
まだ、助けて
But, you know, it's kind of like otophobia.
でも、ほら、やっぱ、 なんか、耳目症とかもさ、
Since they're locked out, so are we.
閉出してるわけだから、 俺らもね
Don't worry, something strange like that happened to you.
安心、 そんな変なことされてんの
It's safe.
安心じゃん
Well, I do it as a hobby.
まあ、 俺、趣味でやるわ
I like people who want to take pictures with a camera.
カメラで、 撮影したい人好きなんですよ
Cute kids also do cosplay.
可愛い子も、 コスプレとかして
Actually, just the edge.
本当は、 ちょっと、エッジだけ
Just a little bit.
ちょっとね
I like that kind of thing, but it's still early.
そういうのが好きなんですけど、 それはまだ早いんじゃん
For example, that's right, something like that.
例えば、だから、 そうだね、なんか、
This is a cosplay photo conference.
コスプレの 撮影会見です
I just took a picture with my camera,
俺はちょっと、 カメラで撮って、
It's like shooting a scene.
コーズ撮って、 シーンみたいな
If it's cosplay, the face, etc.
コスプレとかだったら、 顔とか、
Not much, ok.
あまり、 まあまあまあ
If it's a spray or something, well, just a little bit.
スプレとかだったら、 まあ、 ちょっとね
Really?
本当に?
If only it was a spray.
スプレだけだったら
That's good, it's fun.
いいよね、楽しいよね
Yes, cosplay.
そう、コスプレ
I used to be an idol, so when I say that,
一応、アイドルやってたんで、 そう いう 時、
For some reason, for the first time, there was a scene,
なんか、初めて、 シーンとかあって、
Cosplay, all sorts of things.
コスプレっていうか、 いろいろ、
Take a picture, so I'll take a look at your face,
撮って、 だから、顔をちょっと、
It's a little scary.
ちょっと怖いよね
Apart from my face, I was also leaked.
顔も別に、 俺も流出したりとか、
That's not the purpose, it's more like a commemorative photo.
そういう目的じゃないから、 記念写真みたいな
Make it a date.
デートにして
It's kind of like the atmosphere.
ちょっと、 雰囲気みたいな
Like the atmosphere.
雰囲気みたいな
Her body looks like a mandy.
体がメンディーみたいな
I guess I'll just do it normally.
普通に、 しようかな
Well, I wonder.
まあ、なんだろう
If possible, as I said earlier,
できればね、 俺、さっきも言ったけど、
I like going through things like this.
こう やって通るのも好きだから
It turned out to be a swimsuit?
結構、水着とかなった?
Have you ever done magazines or photo shoots?
雑誌とか、撮影会とか、 やったことあるでしょ?
By the way, did you wear a swimsuit?
一応、水着とかなった?
I didn't take a picture.
撮らず
That's why I wanted to take a photo of it in a swimsuit-like fashion.
だから、水着みたいな感じで、 撮りたいから
Swimsuits, underwear, etc.
水着っていうか、 下着とか
It's underwear.
下着です
I also like things that look like swimsuits.
水着みたいなのも好き
Just some underwear.
ちょっと、 下着とか
Above, because I want to take a picture.
上、 撮りたいから
Do not flush outside.
外に、 流さない
Even I understand that.
それ、私だって分かる
Please do it so that I don't understand.
分からないように、 していただく
OK、OK
nice.
いいね
Of course, money too.
もちろん、お金もね
From me, side.
私から、 サイド
delicious?
美味しい?
cute.
かわいい
Let's do it lightly, shall we?
軽く、ちょっと やろうか
nice.
いいね
May I ask you to shake my hand?
握手してもらっていいですか?
Were you doing this?
これやってた?
I was doing it.
やってました
amazing.
すごい
sweat.
汗
fun.
楽しみ
Like this.
こんな感じで
Are you filming it on video?
ビデオで撮るんですか?
Yes, I always watch videos.
そう、俺はいつも、 ビデオ
Let's take pictures, have a photo session, etc.
撮るっしょ、 撮影会とか
What kind of camera do you use?
どんなカメラで撮る?
But you can take pictures of it.
でも、これ写真 撮れるんだよ
Take a nice shot and snap a photo.
いいショットで 写真、 カシャっと撮って
In the video, there aren't too many faces, legs, etc.
ビデオであんまり 顔とか、 足とか、
Just the body.
体だけ
It's not shown, so not much.
映ってないんで、 あんまり
The atmosphere is nice, isn't it?
ちょっと雰囲気はいいでしょ?
I mean, the atmosphere.
雰囲気っていうか
It's the atmosphere.
雰囲気ですよ
Good.
よいしょ
I can't help it.
しょうがない
I like your great style.
すごいスタイルいいね
Is it a hand?
手ですか?
Look at your hands.
手見して
cute.
かわいい
Hands are cute.
手、 かわいい
Your hands are sweaty.
手汗かいてるね
Sweaty hands.
手汗
Are you nervous?
緊張してる?
a little bit.
ちょっと
Handle me a little.
ちょっと手どけて
Amazing, beautiful.
すごい、綺麗
Have you ever taken something like an image video?
イメージビデオみたいに撮ったことない?
There are image videos.
イメージビデオとかはあります
There is, right?
あるでしょ
Well, it's kind of like that.
まあ、なんかその ちょっと
Something like that.
なんか さ
I saw your cosplay just now, but it's not there.
コスプレがさ さっき見たけど ないんだね、
This hotel.
このホテル
Was there no cosplay?
コスプレなかったんですか?
Well, just the outfit.
まあ、その服装だけ
got it.
わかりました
Can I have you stand for a moment?
ちょっと立ってもらっていいですか?
This is fine.
これで大丈夫です
It's amazing.
すげえいいよ
that's right.
そうです
Is there like a signature pose?
決めポーズみたいなのある?
Like a pose.
ポーズみたいな
That's the way it is as a group.
グループ的にそんな感じだもんね
It's like cleaning.
なんか、清掃なの
That's amazing.
すごいな
Are you losing your hair?
脱毛してる?
I am doing.
してます
Are you uploading it?
アップしてる?
You're doing it.
してるよね
on second thoughts.
や っぱり
Lower your face a little?
顔をちょっと 下?
Down.
下ね
Like revealing blue clothes.
露出が青い服とかね
My face is falling.
顔落ちちゃってます
It hasn't fallen.
落ちちゃってない
It hasn't fallen off much.
あんまり落ちちゃってない
It doesn't really fall off.
あんまりっていうか、落ちちゃわない
Yeah.
うん
Well, it's a hobby, so I'm the only one who sees it.
まあ、そのなんか 趣味なので 俺しか見ないっていうか
Even so, it would be bad if it leaked outside.
それでもあんま外に漏れたら まずいので
Can I have you turn around for a moment?
ちょっと後ろ向いてもらっていいですか?
I really want to touch it.
めっちゃ触りたくなっちゃう
Something...
なんか...
It's so short, amazing.
なんか、すごい 短いよね、すごい
It's all good now.
もうなんか、いいっすよ
You can sit down.
座っていいっすよ
It's okay to sit down.
座 っていいっすよ
I wish I had cosplay, all kinds of things, well...
コスプレがね、あればね いろんな なんか まあ、
It's okay.
大丈夫ですよ
I mean, like I said earlier, just a little bit.
なんか、ほらさっきも言ったけど ちょっと、
I wonder what it is, a swimsuit?
なんだろう 水着?
You said swimsuits are fine, right?
水着とかは大丈夫 って言ってたでしょ?
If it's a swimsuit...
水着だったら...
That's the kind of cosplay I want to photograph.
そういう、撮りたいのっていう コスプレないからさ
Because there's time.
時間もあれだから
It looks like a swimsuit, right?
水着みたいなでしょ?
Do you have swimsuits?
水着は あるんですか?
underwear?
下着?
It's like a swimsuit, right?
その、水着みたいなもんじゃん?
No, it's different when it comes to underwear.
いや、下着やったら 違うんで
Isn't your underwear a little bad?
下着はちょっとよくない?
Hey, underwear is no good.
ちょっと、下着は ダメです
Just a little bit, just a little bit
ちょっと、なんか ちょっとだけ
Just a hand...
ちょっと 手...
You often took pictures of me in swimsuits, right?
水着とかよく撮ったでしょ?
If a swimsuit is a swimsuit, underwear is a little different.
水着は 水着だったら 下着とかはちょっと違うんで
real?
ほんと?
Didn't you just say it was a little nice?
さっきちょっといいって言ってたじゃん?
Is it underwear?
下 着 下着ですか?
There's no cosplay.
コスプレないんだもん
Cosplay.
コ スプレがさ
Hey, so I'll add that.
ちょっと、だからその プラスしますよ
Please take care of that.
その お手当てをね
So I'll wait a little while.
だから、ちょっと待ってます
Is it no good?
ダメですか?
Okay.
よ いしょ
Hey, for example, for example, for example,
ちょっと、例えば 例えばね 例えばね、
What do you think about this?
なんかちょっとこれ どうかな?
Can I take a look?
って 見ていいですか?
Isn't it good?
いいやろ?
It's too early, I guess.
早えな、なんか
The reaction.
反応が
Can I see it?
見ていいっす?
Like.
みたいな
for example
例えば
Is it underwear?
下 着とかですか?
Yeah, yeah.
そうそうそう
Yes, that's it.
そう、そんなんだよな
Your body.
体をね
It doesn't show your face, right?
顔映さないですよね?
Not much, not much.
あんまり、あんまり
I don't care because I'm the only one looking at that atmosphere.
その雰囲気ちょっとチラッと 俺しか見ないから別に
It's kind of a hobby, so I don't think it'll ever go anywhere.
なんか 趣味だし、別に どっか出るわけないし ほら、
As I said earlier, my personal information is registered, so it's okay.
さっきも言ったけど 俺の個人情報とか 登録してるから大丈夫で
Sho?
しょ?
Don't worry.
安 心しろ
We're both dangerous, that's it.
お互いヤバいじゃん、それ
copper?
どう?
that.
それ
No pressure together.
無圧一緒
You're grinning a little.
ちょっとニヤニヤしてるじゃん
No, it's not.
いや、ないです
Please show your face a little bit.
これちょっと顔も 出してもらって ちょっとね、
It's not that simple, but...
そんなかっつりとんないけど で、
Well, there are some rules for changing clothes.
まあ、なんか そういう、ちょっと 着替えルール まあ、
Something about my body, if you can call it that.
なんか 体、なんていうか、そう
I feel like I want to take care of myself.
体取りたいなっていう感じです
That's all, right?
これ だけですよね?
Oh, are you okay?
あ、大丈夫?
Fufufufu.
ふ っふっふ
I'm used to it.
なれてる
It's swollen.
ふくらってますね
No pressure together.
無圧一緒
So cute.
かわいいなぁ
Oh, just a little bit, Masa.
あれ、軽く ちょっとなんか、まさ、
Is it a touch or a massage?
触るっていうか マッサージみたいな マッサージですか?
Yeah, yeah.
そうそうそう
lightly?
軽く?
It's kind of elaborate, isn't it?
なんか、凝ってるでしょ?
Well, my shoulders are fine.
まあ、肩は結構
Is it elaborate?
凝ってる?
What is that?
何、あれ?
Um, practice, practice, I feel like I'm tired of dancing.
あの、練習、練習っていうか ダンス疲れみたいな
I also dance.
ダンスもやってます
You're doing it.
やってるよね
It's elaborate.
凝ってるわ
凝ってる
This area is also kind of thin.
この辺も なんか おぉ、細いね、
arm.
腕
amazing.
すごい
Well, it's kind of a light skinship, isn't it?
まあ、なんか、軽い スキンシップですよね
It's like a handshake event.
握手会みたいな
Isn't there a hug event with fans?
ファンの人とハグ会みたいな、ないの?
No hugs.
ハグはないです
It's just a handshake.
握手くらいです
Maybe a handshake?
握手くらいか
Shaking hands is just holding hands all the time.
握手ってさ、 ずっと手握ってるだけじゃん
Wait, it's not a handshake.
ちょっと、 握手じゃないよね
With this hand, or should I say this hand,
この手でさ、 この手っていうか、
The story I heard was from a fan...
俺聞いたのの話はさ、 ファンの人がさ、
Rub your own bodily fluids on your hands.
手にね、 自分のさ、体液をさ、 擦り、
Put it on before shaking hands, knead it in,
握手する前につけてね、 練り込んで、
So this is how you touch it.
それでこうやって触るんだって
Is it true?
本当ですか?
Don't you know about that?
そういうの知らない?
I learned this for the first time.
初めて知りました
Have you ever been slimy?
ぬめってしたことない?
When you shake hands like this.
こうやって握手したときに
It feels kind of disgusting.
なんか、 気持ち悪いみたいな
Maybe there is.
もしかしたらあるかもしれないです
That's how you do it.
やるんだって、そうやって
That's what the fans said.
そうやってファンの人が言ってた
I thought it was disgusting.
気持ち悪いって思って
Moreover, with the hands that touched me like this,
しかも、こうやって触った 手で、
I'm going to go to the bathroom and prepare it myself.
これままトイレ行って、 自分で仕込むんだって
With this hand.
この手で
Isn't it dangerous?
やばくない?
Don't you understand something like that?
そういうのなんか、 察しない?
But, I guess I'm doing it.
でも、 してるんだろうな、みたいな
Do you really think so?
やっぱ思う?
There were times when I thought about it.
思うときはありました
I did it, everyone.
してんだよ、みんな
Those are cute hands.
可愛い手だね
amazing.
すごい
Why not do something like this?
こういうのは、 しないか
Her legs are also thin.
足も細い
Let me give you a massage.
マッサージしてさせて
Very thin.
すごい細い
Smooth.
滑らかな
Your legs are tired too.
足も疲れてるでしょ
Are you tired?
疲れてる?
I'm tired because I'm moving around a lot.
いろいろ動かしてるんで、 疲れてます
Are you going to cover your face?
顔面被るんですか?
That's more exciting.
そのほうが、 興奮っていう
Isn't it interesting?
面白くない?
面白いですかね
Hey, it's just underwear.
ちょっとさ、 下着ですよ
Open it a little.
ちょっと開いて
What's cool about boobs?
おっぱいって何かっこいい?
It's a secret.
内緒です
secret?
内緒?
Just a little massage.
ちょっとマッサージすね
No.
ダメです
It's not a massage, is it?
マッサージじゃないじゃないですか
It's cracking right away.
すぐ割れてる
No.
ダメです
It's quite soft.
結構柔らかいね
It feels really soft.
めっちゃ柔らかい気がする
No?
ダメ?
Well then, can I judge the swimsuit?
じゃあさ、 水着審査していいですか?
I want to wear a swimsuit.
水着したいですよ
I thought it was a swimsuit
水着だと思って
hey.
ね
Let's take a look from above?
ゆ っくり、 上から 見ちゃう?
Is it underneath too?
下もですか?
You're used to it now, right?
今度慣れてるでしょ?
I thought it was a swimsuit.
水着だと思って
We're together.
一緒じゃん
I'm used to it.
慣れてる
I'm slow.
足遅い
It's late.
遅いね
Hey.
ねえ
It's like being an idol.
アイドルって感じだよね
Did something happen to your breasts?
おっぱい何かあったの?
Please don't get too close.
あまり、近づかないでください
That's terrible.
ひどいな
Stay away.
近 づかない
Look behind you.
後ろ見て
That's naughty.
やらしい
It's meat.
肉だ
With Petta, let's take some pose-like shots.
ペッタでさ、 ポーズみたいなの撮ろう?
Well then,
じゃあ、
Close your chest and look up.
胸 寄せてさ、 上目遣い
Ah, nice, nice.
あ、いいねいいね
Photo opportunity.
シャッターチャンス
Pose.
ポーズ
What pose do you like?
どんなポーズがいいですか?
Put your hands together.
両手をさ、こう
Ah, yes, yes.
あ、そうそうそう
Sexy.
セクシーな
Ah, yes, yes.
あ、そうそうそう
It's a photo opportunity.
シャッターチャンスだよ
Take care.
気にして
That's good.
いいっすね
Good.
いいっす
amazing.
すごい
I can't see much of your face.
あんまり顔は、 映ってないよ
It's not shown.
映ってないよ
Yeah.
うん
Could you please stand up on your feet?
ちょっと足、 こう、立ててもらえ?
The M word.
M字
Get behind me.
後ろに手ついてよ
Even the face.
顔も
Are you okay.
大丈夫
The face is not shown.
顔は映ってない
Not much.
あんまり
nice.
いいね
Hey, look, I'm gonna do something that's going to stick out my butt.
ちょっと、なんか、ほら、お尻つきだすやつやって
You'll do it in gravure, right?
グラビアでやるでしょ
Ah, yes, yes.
あ、そうそうそう
Wow, that's amazing.
うわ、すげー
Awesome.
すげー
Wait a minute.
ちょっと待ってね
I'll give you a little massage.
ちょっとマッサージしてあげる
It looks like her butt is also quite broken.
なんか、 お尻も結構折らしい
It's connected to your waist.
腰と繋がってんだって
it's okay.
大丈夫です
Are you okay?
大丈夫?
Well, somehow,
まあ、なんか、
Hey, no.
ちょっと、 ダメ
It's like, just a little bit.
なんか、ちょっとだけ、みたいな
No, no.
いや、ダメ
No.
ダメです
Hey, no.
ねぇ、ダメです
Somehow,
なんか、
Well, that's fine.
まあ、 ちょっと、いいじゃん
No.
ダ メです
I can't even see my face.
顔も映ってない
Well, it's fine for a while.
まあ、ちょっと、いいじゃん
No.
ダメです
I can't even see my face.
顔も映ってない
I just don't really understand.
なんか、 ちょっと、 あんまりわかんない
What is it?
なんですか?
Just a little bit.
ちょっと、 ちょっとだけ
Hey, that.
ねぇ、あれ
No.
ダメです
Because only the body will be shown, From now on, only the body will be shown.
体しか映らないから、 これからは体しか映らないから
I can see your face too.
顔も映ってる
It's reflected, isn't it?
映ってますよね
It's going to show up.
映っちゃうんだって
Please do not display it.
映さないようにしてください
It's really no good.
本当にダメです
No.
ダメです
I saw it a little while ago.
ちょっと見えたよ、さっき
No.
ダメです
Please delete it.
消してください
All you have to do is turn it off.
消せばいいじゃん
No.
ダメです
Delete.
削除する
Let's look at it together and delete it later.
後で一緒に見て、削除しよう
Just a little bit worth it.
もう、ちょっとだけ、 お値啊
Sorry for the price.
お値、すいません
No.
ダ メです
It's worth it.
お値ぁ
Please lend it to me.
貸 してください
貸 して 下 さい
Do love enseñ?
ラ ブ enseñを行?
Please don't raise it.
上げないでください
I'll give you some money too.
お金もちょっとあげるし
No, no.
ダメです、ダメです
Only take the body.
体しか取ってないで
Really, really.
ほんと、ほんと
it's okay.
大丈夫だよ
I mean, look.
だってなんか、ほら
Style, you know, kind of, you know.
スタイル、ほら、なんか、ほら
There's something about me wanting to take a nude photo.
ちょっとヌード取りたいなっていうのあるじゃん
It was there.
せっかくあったし
I'll pay too.
お金も払うし
If it gets found out, it will be bad and no good.
バレたらまずいでダメです
I won't find out, I won't find out.
バレない、バレない
You'll never find out.
絶対バレない
I don't know if you have it.
あんたにがあるか分かんないんで
No.
ダメです
I can see your face too.
顔も映ってる
It's seriously not showing right now.
今、マジで映ってない
No.
ダ メです
It's seriously okay.
マジで大丈夫
So, let's take a look?
じゃあ、見てみる?
It doesn't show up, right?
映ってないでしょ?
Take a look at this situation.
この状態で ちょっと、見てみて
Look, this is all you can see.
ほら、これしか映ってない
No.
ダメ
ダメって
It's okay, it's okay.
大丈夫、大丈夫
Just this, just this.
これだけ、これだけ
I really haven't.
本当にしてないよ
Seriously.
マジで
It's over now.
もう終わりです
It's already early.
もう早い
Isn't it over?
終わんない?
Because it won't end.
終わんないから
You want it to end, right?
終 わりたいでしょ?
Cute
可愛 いじゃ
yeah...
ん...
early.
早い
Isn't it over?
終わんない?
Because it won't end.
終わんないから
You want it to end, right?
終わりたいでしょ?
It's going to end really soon.
もう本当にすぐ終わる
It's cute.
可愛いじゃん
Don't take it.
取っちゃえな
I won't forget to touch it.
触るの忘れないです
Show me, then.
見せて、じゃあ
Do it while showing your face.
顔、顔を映しながらする
Are you okay.
大丈夫
So, just, uh, stand up.
じゃあ、ちょっと、えーっと、立って
Ah, good, that.
あーいい、それ
Show it, show it.
映して、映して
I can't see it with my eyes, so stay behind me.
目で見えないから、後ろやってて
yes.
そう
I started remembering it.
覚え出しちゃった
My face is shown, but it's not.
顔、映して、映ってないですよ
I like the style.
いいね、スタイルが
She's an idol.
アイドルだね
nice.
いいね
That's amazing.
すごいよ
Don't touch it, don't touch it, then.
触んない、触んない、じゃあ
Wait a minute, see you next time.
ちょっと、じゃあ、また
It happened like this.
こうなって
Yeah, yeah.
そうそうそう
Stretch your back.
背伸ばしてね
It's okay, it's okay.
大丈夫、大丈夫
The bottom is no good.
下は、下はダメです
Shall we choose this?
これにしましょう?
no.
いや
A little more, a little more.
もうちょい、もうちょい
I've shown you enough.
もう十分見せました
Are you okay?
大丈夫?
That's why they say the face is no good either.
だから顔もダメって言ってるじゃないですか
It can't be helped, can it?
ちょっとしょうがないんでしょ
I don't like it.
嫌だ
Are you okay?
大丈夫?
Just a little bit, uh, kind of, um.
ちょっとさ、あの、なんか、その、
Actually, I just want to take nude photos.
なんていうか、ヌードだけ撮りたい
No, I already, already, already took the picture.
いや、 もう、もう、もう、撮った、
I took a picture.
撮りました
I didn't take a picture.
撮ってない
No more.
これ以上ダメです
You took the picture, right?
撮ったじゃないですか
No, again.
いや、また
I'm not taking pictures anymore.
撮ってないよ、もう
Well then, just a moment.
じゃあ、ちょっと
Are you okay?
大丈夫?
Can't you take it off?
脱がせない?
I can't take it off, so, uh, only my legs are open.
脱がせないから、 えーっと、 脚だけ開いてるじゃん
What do you think?
どうでしょ?
Just open your legs?
脚だけ開いてみ?
No.
ダメです
I'm a little curious about the swimsuit.
水着、ちょっとなんか気になる
Hey, oh, that's it.
ねぇ、あ、もうです
Okay, okay, what's up?
よいしょ、よし、どうした
Let's end this now.
もう終わりにしましょう
It's okay, it's okay.
大丈夫、大丈夫
You promised not to show your face, right?
顔も映さないって約束だったじゃないですか
It's not showing.
映してないもん
Not much.
あんまり
It doesn't seem like much, does it?
あんまりって、写ってるじゃないですか
No, you can check it later and delete it.
いや、あとで確認して、消せばいいじゃん
Do you really want to delete it?
本当に消しますか?
No, I will never delete it.
いや、絶対消さないですね
No, I'll check it after it's finished.
いや、終わった後に確認しよう
No, no, no.
ダ メ です、ダメです
It's fine when I'm just doing it.
とりあえずやってるときはいいし
It's just the body, and moreover.
体だけだし、しかも
Hasn't it already been shown?
もう、映したじゃないですか
No, make it a little smaller.
いや、ちょっと小さくして
please.
お願い
It won't end because it won't end.
終わらないって、終わらないから
It's over now.
もう終わりです
It won't end, it won't end.
終わらない、終われないんだって
Hey, hey.
ちょっと、ちょっと
I don't like it anymore.
もう嫌だ
Are you okay,
大丈夫、
Are you okay.
大丈夫
Please stop using your hands.
手 は、手はやめてください
I understand, I understand.
分 かった、分かった
I don't touch it.
触ったりはしない
No, no.
ダメ、ダメ
You're definitely trying to take pictures, aren't you?
絶対撮ろうとしてるじゃないですか
My face wasn't good either.
顔もダメだった
what?
何?
I'm going home, really.
帰りますよ、本当に
Really.
本当に
But it's okay to say I'll give you the money.
でも、 お金渡すって言っていいでしょ
But you promised not to take pictures and it would be bad for your skin.
でも、撮らないって、肌皮ダメって約束だったじゃないですか
I said no, right?
ダ メって言ったじゃないですか
I'm not saying that skin is good.
肌皮はいいって言ってないです
Didn't I tell you that I only wore underwear?
下着だけだったらって話したじゃないですか
Don't even take pictures of my face.
顔も撮らないでって
That's a different story.
話が違います
Just a little bit, please.
ちょっとだけ、お願い
Because it won't end.
終わんないから
Well, I can't return it yet.
じゃあ、まだ返せない
You get it.
分かるでしょ
it hurts?
痛い?
Please stop.
やめてください
Just a little bit, please.
ちょっとだけ、お願い
Is it okay for a moment?
一瞬でいい?
I don't like it.
嫌です
Are you okay?
大丈夫?
I don't like it.
嫌です
No, it's fine, I've already taken pictures up to this point.
いや、いいじゃん、もうここまで撮ってんだから
Because I don't touch it.
触らないから
Sleep?
寝て?
No, no.
ダメ、ダメ
Just with your hands.
ちょっと手だけで
No.
ダメ
Just with your hands.
手だけで
I don't like it, hey.
嫌だ、ねえ
I don't like it.
嫌だ
Are you okay?
大丈夫?
Isn't this sleeping?
これ、寝てないの?
I don't like it.
嫌だ
I'm taking pictures.
撮ってる
撮ってるよ
You said you didn't take a picture of your face.
顔は撮ってないって言ってんじゃん
No.
ダメ
I'll erase it.
消すし
That's no good.
ダメですね
I was able to take some more pictures.
もうちょっと撮れたよ
No.
ダメ
I'm going home.
帰ります
Don't give me money.
お金渡すねえよ
I'll contact the club.
連絡しますよ、クラブの方に
No, I don't really care, that's it.
いや、別にさ、だってさ、それ
Because only I can see it.
だって俺しか見えないじゃん
Well, if you saw it, yeah.
見たとしてはまあ、うん
Don't you see it?
見ないか
I don't see it.
見ない
Not really.
別にさ
did?
した?
I?
俺?
cute?
可愛い?
No, just a little.
いや、ちょっとだけ
You're sleeping.
寝てるね
I was spilling it.
こぼしてた
oh.
おー
Wow, so beautiful.
うわ、めっちゃ綺麗
Oh, that's amazing.
おー、すごい
It's so beautiful.
め っちゃ綺麗
touch?
触る?
No, wait a minute, um.
いや、ちょっと、あの
That's all.
これだけ
oh.
おー
It's so beautiful.
め っちゃ綺麗
I'm tingling.
ヒクヒクしてる
Oh, I'm tingling.
おー、ヒクヒクしてる
No?
ダメ?
Is that no good?
そんなダメ?
No.
ダメ
Alright, alright, alright, by myself.
じゃあさ、じゃあさ、じゃあさ、自分でさ、
This is opening your pussy.
これさ、自分でおまんこ開いてるじゃん
yes.
はい